There really aren't many espers, are there?
"Potato"
"Potato" All of these people have
walked by and not one has stood out.
"Potato"
You aren't tricking me, are you?
There really haven't been any.
Hey, are you on a date here?
Who is this obviously special guy?
Hanazawa-kun...
Sorry, this is an emergency.
I'm gonna borrow him for a bit.
Him?
Someone's using my name and fighting?
Yeah. It's a student from
Salt Middle School.
You might know him.
He's back there.
You should go see for yourself.
Ritsu...
What are you doing?
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
We'll be able to find our answers
1%, 2%, 3%, 4%, 5%, 6%, 7%, 8%, 9%, 10%...
11%, 12%, 13%, 14%, 15%,
16%, 17%, 18%, 19%, 20%...
21%, 22%, 23%, 24%, 25%...
Admiration, troubles, pump up
26%, 27%, 28%, 29%, 30%...
Searching for yourself, telepathy
31%, 32%, 33%, 34%, 35%...
Asking for the impossible, psycho punch
36%, 37%, 38%, 39%, 40%...
Youthful Salt Splash
Mob? Mob? What do you want?
Mob? Mob? Why do you want?
Mob? Mob? Who do you want?
Move! Move! Just like Mob!
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
Even if you hold onto happiness and sadness
Your life is your own, OK?
It's OK you are not special
We'll all be able to find our answers
81%, 82%, 83%, 84%, 85%,
86%, 87%, 88%, 89%, 90%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
"Mob Psycho 100" 91%, 92%, 93%,
94%, 95%, 96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
"The Older Brother Bows"
"~Destructive Intent~"
Nii-san... What are you doing here?
I could ask you the same thing, Ritsu.
Oh, that's his younger brother.
Someone just showed up.
Who are all of these people on the ground?
Did you do this, Ritsu?
Ritsu?
Yes, I did this.
I'm not so boorish as to
watch siblings fight.
Really? You really did this, Ritsu?
It's true.
It's not true.
There's no way you would do this.
I mean... seriously...
Nii-san, I did this.
I obtained psychic powers.
Huh?
Wait, Ritsu! You're up against Shigeo!
Shut up, Dimple.
Tch! He's drunk with power.
This is why I hate brats.
I'm not gonna hang around
for a battle I know he'll lose!
Dimple?!
That's fine.
I've got the feel of it now.
Nii-san, I've realized
something very important.
Ritsu, what's wrong?
If something's bothering you...
You really do have psychic powers...
I missed...
Ritsu...
Congratulations!
You've wanted to use them for so long!
Do you remember?
When you were little, you used to cry your
eyes out because you couldn't bend spoons.
Who would've thought that now--
That hadn't changed until recently.
Just listen, Nii-san.
I've always wanted psychic powers.
And I've always admired you, Nii-san.
Aw, you're making me blush...
But that was a big misunderstanding.
Huh?
I couldn't handle my inferiority complex
and fear towards you,
so I was protecting myself
by thinking it was admiration.
I was scared of you.
I never knew what you'd do
if you got stressed out.
We could never even
have a fight as brothers...
Because I have no way
to protect myself from your powers.
So, I did my best not to
stress you out in any way.
Now, that's just a humiliating past.
I tried so hard for so long,
no matter how crazy it made me...
And yet,
you never worked hard
in your life, so why?
But now, I've obtained them.
Now I don't have to be scared anymore.
The delusional admiration is gone.
Actually...
Now I've just lost all interest...
The buddy-buddy brothers act
ends now, Nii-san.
Ritsu... I can tell. That's a lie.
Face me, right now!
Hit me with your powers!
But I guess it's true...
I'm your brother, Ritsu.
Hey, Ritsu.
Half of that is true, right?
I'm terribly sorry that
my little brother hurt you.
Please still be friends
with him from now on.
Huh?
What? You're his older brother?
Yes. I'm very sorry.
You idiot! You think
that's enough to be forgiven?!
You need to grovel first!
O-Okay...
Hey... Stop.
Why, Nii-san?
What are you doing?!
Ritsu... It's no use
trying to get rid of me...
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 7%"
Because we're brothers.
Hello?
I'd like a status update.
It's been ten minutes since you
reported that you've found the target.
What are you doing?
I'm just observ--
Are you an idiot?
Hurry up and bring him here.
All right.
"Sakurai"
Actually, just in case, send a photo.
"Sakurai" It'll be troublesome
if you bring the wrong brat.
It'll be troublesome
Yeah, yeah...
How dare he mock me?
There you go. It's sent.
Confirmed.
There's no doubt that
that's Kageyama Shigeo.
Right?
It's just as the data
from the Awakening Lab says.
What an exaggerated name.
It's embarrassing to say.
Listen up.
Don't mess this up.
The more information we leak,
the more annoying it'll be.
Don't play around.
Yeah, yeah...
Acting all high-and-mighty...
Now, then...
The tables have turned!
White T Poison!
If you don't want us to beat the crap out
of your brother, get your face over here.
Hold it. You shouldn't do that.
Huh?
I don't want to see
anyone else hurting people,
or anyone else getting hurt.
Who the hell do you think
you are, small fry?!
Only the strongest can give orders.
And the strongest will rule.
Just how pathetic are these people?
The strongest one here is...
You're exactly right.
Who are you?
--Ritsu!
--What?
--Who's that?
--Who the hell are you?!
The strongest will rule.
It's such an obvious thing
that you forget about it.
You guys figure that
if you're strong at fighting,
you can rule your school
and turfs, right?
That's cute. You should keep it up.
But he's on a different level.
You guys don't have
a chance of beating him.
So I'm going to remove him
from the fighting grounds.
You can continue your squabbling in peace.
I'll be taking him.
Hold it! He's our target!
You're just an outsider!
--How dare you do that to our boss?!
--Hey, don't.
--T-Too strong...
--That's not fair...
You thugs are such simple creatures...
My little brother...
N-Nii-san...
Did I hit him too hard?
Well, if he dies,
I'd say he was just unlucky.
Hey, you good-for-nothing.
What's with that rebellious stare?
It's not! I was just looking...
--Grovel, and apologize to me.
--Huh?
We're reviewing the scene
you were playing out earlier.
I know! All of you should grovel.
Will this make you a little more willing?
If you don't grovel, I'll kill all of you.
What a great sight!
It's a great lesson for idiots
who mistake youth and freedom.
I've got one piece of advice
for the rest of your rotten lives.
Try to live your lives walking on
the side of the road as much as possible,
so you don't cause anyone else trouble.
See ya, brats.
Damn it!
What was that?
That's...
Ritsu!
You, too, brat?
N-Nii-san...
I wasn't told about a psychic brother.
Let go of my brother...
...or else...
Oh, so you've put up a barrier?
I'm not supposed to use
these powers against others,
but this is different!
Don't underestimate me, brat.
I remember now!
He's the adult esper I saw before...
There are ways to deal with
little esper brats like you.
Telekinetic Helix!
"Telekinetic Helix"
He's attacking again. I don't want
to become an adult like him.
Cry.
Huh?
You're so light. You fly up really well.
It hurts...
I can't exhale...
...or inhale...
My stomach is hot...
You surprised?
My powers rip through
your barrier like an excavator.
Nii-san!
Stand up.
You're going to protect
your little brother, right?
Oh, crap.
He's hitting him way too much.
--You can't be serious...
--He's gonna die.
Seriously?
Nii-san?
S-Stop...
Please, stop!
Stop!
Just take me!
That's what you wanted, right?
That's a wise decision,
but I'm an asshole.
I don't like that look on your face...
That hostile little face!
Hey, you.
This is the first time this has happened.
Can you feel it?
My animosity?
"Mob Psycho 100"
He made me put my hands to the ground...
A brat like that...
I can't get away!
That guy is finished.
Hey, mister, who did terrible things to us...
Just so you know, this is all your fault.
Don't ever show your face
in front of us again.
Telekinetic Helix!
It's hard?! It's nothing like before...
Wow...
Hey, did you see that?
What was that?
What's going on?
You're kidding!
Energy Bomb!
You're actually making me
use my trump card...
Nii-san!
Why won't he fall over?
At this rate, things won't end well...
I know! If I bring him here...
Damn it! What's with this brat?
H-He's strong!
If I don't put up my guard,
I'll be knocked out in an instant.
Whoa!
Yeah! Get him!
To think a guy like that existed...
Hey, look!
It's a white T-shirt!
That's it!
He's not White T Poison's older brother...
He's the infamous shadow leader
at Salt Middle School...
White T Poison!
Taking him on in a battle
of abilities isn't good.
I don't have a choice.
The mission comes first.
He's got a knife! Look out!
Shut up, brat!
If you're not going to give up, I'll end it.
The next move will be the last.
Take this, brat!
Damn it! This barrier's so thick!
My knife won't go through!
Just kidding!
What?
I don't like using this stuff,
but I don't have time.
I guess you've all seen my face.
As annoying as it is, I'm gonna
have to make you all disappear.
C-Crap!
--Run!
-H-Hurry!
Do you really think I'll let you
get away after everything you saw?
Impossible! I can't take him on anymore!
You're coming with me.
Did we survive?
--Yeah! --We did it!
--We're saved!
--Awesome!
--You're amazing!
You saved our lives!
Huh?
He's standing while unconscious.
Get away from him.
It's still dangerous to be near him.
You're from Black Vinegar Middle School...
I can't believe someone was
able to push him this far.
They're no ordinary person.
The guy and Ritsu are gone.
We were a bit late.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
This is rock salt from the Himalayas.
It goes great with pasta or meat.
Let's perform the exorcism with this.
Your shoulders feel heavy, right?
Yes. A fortuneteller told me
there was something on them.
So, they just told her that and
took the money? How irresponsible.
All right.
Wh-What are you doing?
Ghosts are weak against salt.
First, we'll weaken it
with the rock salt powder.
And this scraping noise by your ears...
This will be really annoying to spirits
that want to live in a quiet place,
so they should leave.
Next!
We'll use the hard edges of
the rock salt and do a massage
to loosen up your tense muscles
and improve your blood flow.
We'll place a hot towel on your face,
and shut out the spirit's
visual interference.
Along with using aroma oils
to maximize your relaxation,
we'll light some incense that spirits hate.
S-Such a wonderful smell!
Aroma Runaway Express!
"Aroma Runaway Express"
"Aroma Runaway Express" This is one of Reigen's special
moves, where he sends his clients on a beauty trip
"Aroma Runaway Express"
that relaxes the body and soul.
I feel so much younger.
That's great!
Thank goodness there was
no actual spirit this time,
but this is the first time
Mob didn't show up to work on time.
I'm gonna have to lecture him
when I see him next.
Nii-san.
If there's anything troubling you,
let me know.
I'll be there to listen anytime.
Nii-san, is something bothering you?
Are you okay, Nii-san?
If something's bothering you, I'll listen.
Thanks, Ritsu, but I'm fine.
It's nothing.
I see.
Ritsu? Ritsu?
I see...
I'm sorry I didn't realize it sooner.
Are you awake, Kageyama-kun?
Hanazawa-kun... where are we?
My apartment.
Dimple-kun told me everything.
H-Hey, Shigeo...
Dimple...
What's going on?
Why were you with Ritsu?
Well...
And Ritsu was kidnapped.
Dimple...
Is this your doing?
It's a misunderstanding!
I don't know who those guys are!
I know who they are.
Huh?
They've been following me around
for a few years now.
Is that why you're living by yourself
when you're in middle school?
Let me give you a warning.
Stay away from them.
Stay away?
You'll die.
It's an organization called Claw,
formed by dangerous espers.
They want a revolution
and aim to turn the world on its head.
Their ability to function
as a group is first-rate,
and they have over a hundred espers.
You're kidding, right?
A hundred...
There are plenty of facilities
across the world that are trying to
manufacture psychic powers.
But the only one to succeed at it is Claw.
Apparently they take child espers
who have yet to mature,
brainwash them, and raise them as soldiers.
They aren't as powerful as us Naturals,
but if you underestimate them,
their sheer numbers will easily crush you.
You sure know a lot about them.
I heard all about them from one of
their guys who tried to kidnap me before.
Though I taught him a lesson.
Basically, they're from
a very dangerous world.
Shigeo, you could've been killed back there!
It doesn't matter...
Ritsu, my little brother, was kidnapped.
I'm going to go save him.
Do you want to die?
No, not at all.
Then calm down.
But I think I can win.
All right.
But why are they after your little brother?
I have no idea.
Ah! That's right!
There's a research facility where
people like you were gathering.
Ritsu was going there recently, too.
Ritsu was?
So, the information
must have leaked from there.
Want to check it out?
Though, I have
a terrible feeling about this...
I'll lead you there.
This is terrible...
How could they do this to civilians?
They're unconscious, but not dead.
Wh-Who are you?! Where did he go?
The guy with the sword!
You'll need to answer our questions first.
Did you sell Kageyama Ritsu's
information to Claw?
Claw? What's that?
Kageyama Ritsu?
I don't know who that is.
The one I invited here
was Kageyama Shigeo-kun.
That's me.
That's you?!
This all started with a misunderstanding,
and yet they really managed
to awaken Ritsu.
I have no idea what's going on.
Damn it...
And we were finally seeing
some hope in our research, too.
Looks like this guy doesn't know anything.
Where are the other kids?
They were kidnapped...
Is this my fault?
To think there are people like them...
What kind of level of power
did the kids who were kidnapped have?
I'd like to know
to know what we're up against.
Hold on a sec. Who are you guys?
What are you doing, Hanazawa-kun?
Introducing ourselves.
Come on, brats. Hurry up and get out.
Quit dawdling. Keep moving.
Don't make me spank you.
Don't scare them more than necessary.
They'll be useless then.
Kageyama, are you okay?
I'm fine, but we really
shouldn't fight back right now.
Trapped in a suspicious research facility,
Ritsu tries to plot an escape
with the good-for-nothing espers.
Meanwhile, Mob rises to save Ritsu.
That's right, Mob!
That's what you call a man.
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Episode 9:
"'Claw'
~7th Division~."
Option B, the serious course, involves buying
the Blu-rays and the manga volumes.
"'Claw'" "~7th Division~" Option B, the serious course,
involves buying the Blu-rays and the manga volumes.